export const excelQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Which symbol is used to start a formula in Excel?",
    options: ["=", "+", "-", "*"],
    answer: "=",
  },
  {
    question: "Which function finds the largest number?",
    options: ["MAX()", "LARGE()", "BIG()", "TOP()"],
    answer: "MAX()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which shortcut saves a workbook?",
    options: ["Ctrl + X", "Ctrl + V", "Ctrl + S", "Ctrl + C"],
    answer: "Ctrl + S",
  },
  {
    question: "Which chart is best for showing trends over time?",
    options: ["Pie Chart", "Bar Chart", "Line Chart", "Column Chart"],
    answer: "Line Chart",
  },
  {
    question: "Which function counts only numeric values?",
    options: ["COUNTA()", "COUNT()", "COUNTIF()", "SUM()"],
    answer: "COUNT()",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the intersection of a row and column called?",
    options: ["Cell", "Table", "Range", "Block"],
    answer: "Cell",
  },
  {
    question: "Which function returns the average of values?",
    options: ["AVERAGE()", "SUM()", "ROUND()", "MEAN()"],
    answer: "AVERAGE()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which shortcut is used to insert a new worksheet?",
    options: ["Shift + F11", "Ctrl + F11", "Alt + F11", "F11"],
    answer: "Shift + F11",
  },
  {
    question: "Which function returns the current date?",
    options: ["TIME()", "NOW()", "DATE()", "TODAY()"],
    answer: "TODAY()",
  },
  {
    question: "Which Excel feature is used to restrict data entry?",
    options: ["Validation", "Sorting", "Filter", "Formatting"],
    answer: "Validation",
  },
];
